来点甜蜜的我不介意
I sure could go for something sweet.
你要吃点什么吗
Do you want to grab a bite to eat?
我想要的甜蜜不是吃的
Actually, it's not food that I'm craving.
怎么了
What? Is it...
不不  没什么
No, no. It's nothing.
不  我恰好是"没什么"专家
No, no. I happen to be an expert on nothing.
这个表情  可不是没什么
And this. This is not nothing.
好吧
Okay. Fine.
-你知道你会说梦话对吗  -嗯
- Do you know how you talk in your sleep sometimes? - Oh, yeah.
昨晚你说了个名字
Well, last night you said a name.
我猜不是你的名字
Oh... and not your name I'm assuming.
不是
No.
随便说了个名字  别多想嘛
Well, I wouldn't read anything into one random utterance.
说了14遍
14 utterances.
名字是乔丹
And the name was Jordan.
你说了一遍又一遍
You said it over and over again.
乔丹是谁
Who's Jordan?
我不知道
I have no idea.
是女人吗
Is it a woman?
不  没什么
No, it's nothing.
卡塞尔  我知道"没什么"
Castle, I know nothing.
"没什么"是我亲爱的朋友
Nothing is a dear friend of mine.
这个可不是"没什么"
And this. This is not nothing.
是没什么  而且
Yes, it is. Besides...
我大多数的话都毫无意义
Most of what I say is meaningless.
更何况是梦话呢
Why would it be any different when I'm asleep?
这事没完
We're not done here.
得了  卡塞尔  乔丹是谁
Come on, castle. Who is Jordan?
我没什么可隐瞒的  本来就没什么可说的
I got nothing to hide. There's just nothing to tell.
那你怎么这么戒备
Then why are you being so defensive?
我没有
I'm not.
好吧
Okay, fine.
那我等到你睡着好了
I'll just wait until you're asleep.
然后我再问你
And then I'll ask you.
你不能这样做
You can't do that.
拜托  卡塞尔  你才说你没什么可隐瞒的
Come on, Castle. You just said that you had nothing to hide.
在我睡着时审问我
Yeah, but interrogating me in my sleep?
你会用这么卑鄙的招数吗
Would you stoop that low?
谁说我没用过
Who says I haven't already?
早啊  蕾妮
Hey, Lanie.
哇  真是死在巧克力上啊
Wow. Talk about death by chocolate.
不关巧克力的事  卡塞尔
Don't blame it on the chocolate, castle.
死因是子弹
A bullet's what did him in.
那红色的不是覆盆子酱喽
So that red stuff's not raspberry sauce?
恐怕不是  子弹射出伤
Afraid not. Exit wound.
那么他是背后中枪然后跌进桶里
So he was shot in the back and then fell in the mixer?
看起来是的  但在那之前
Looks like, but before that,
他可能和凶手搏斗过
he may have struggled with his attacker.
米黄色纤维
Beige fibers--
在他的表带上发现的
They were caught on his watchband.
鉴证组会拿去分析
C.S.U. will run an analysis.
被害人叫吉米·韦兰  这家店的老板
Vic's name is Jimmy Whelan. He's the owner of the shop.
他没有前科
He has no record...
从背景资料中也看不出谁可能是凶手
And nothing in his bio that points to who did this.
可以排除不满意的顾客
You can rule out dissatisfied customers.
这些东西太好吃了
These things are insanely good.
你居然吃死人的纸杯蛋糕
You're eating a dead man's cupcake?
那边有免费样品
There was free samples.
死亡时间
Time of death?
11点半到12点
Between 11:30 and 12:00.
怎么看出来的
Based on what?
你一下子成了法医吗
All of a sudden, you're an M.E.?
你不是喜欢我扮医生吗
I thought you liked it when I played doctor.
这样说的依据是
I, uh, based the time of death on what
死者助手的话
the vic's assistant told me.
就在那边
Right over there.
托德  告诉我们发生了什么事
Okay, Todd, why don't you just run us through what happened?
吉米让我11点半去送货
Jimmy sent me on a delivery at 11:30--
送一打红丝绒蛋糕到路口的美容院
A dozen red velvets to a beauty shop down the way.
我回来后发现
And when I came back...
吉米是个非常好的人
He's a super-nice guy-- Jimmy.
他认识的人中有没有不这么想的
Well, is there anyone in his life who didn't feel that way?
我不清楚
I'm not sure.
我才在这里工作两周
The truth is, this is only my second week here.
但我离开前他的表现很奇怪
But he was acting real strange right before I left.
怎么奇怪
Strange how?
店外有辆徘徊的车
This car... cruised by the shop,
开得很慢
kinda slow.
他变得紧张
He got all nervous.
那时他就让我离开
That's when he sent me on my run,
好像是故意要支开我
like he wanted to get rid of me.
什么样的车
What kind of car was it?
黑色的68年道奇突击者
It was a black '68 charger r/t.
我比较懂大马力车
I know my muscle cars.
看到司机了吗
Did you see who was driving?
没  我离开时  司机把车停到了街角
No, but whoever it was parked it around the corner as I was leaving.
我回来后  车开走了
When I got back, the car was gone,
吉米死了
And there was Jimmy.
我们需要那辆车的详细描述
Well, we'll need a detailed description of that car.
看来吉米放了不少现金[面团]啊
Looks like Jimmy kept a lot of dough around here.
这里是西点店嘛
It is a bakery.
真好笑
Good one.
箱子是在他办公室找到的
This briefcase was stashed in his office.
五万现金
That's $50,000.
四块钱一个蛋糕
Whoa. At $4 a pop,
得卖12500个
he would have to sell 12,500 cupcakes.
听起来不太可能
That seems unlikely.
托德  你知道这笔钱吗
Todd, what do you know about that money?
不知道  我发誓
Nothing. I swear.
但他对这个箱子非常紧张
But he's real paranoid about that case.
一周两次  他会从保险柜里拿出来
Twice a week, he'd take it out of the safe
带去斯坦顿岛
and take it with him down to staten island.
-去做什么  -他说在那里有生意
- What for? - Just said he had business there.
显然吉米做的不仅仅是纸杯蛋糕的生意
Well, obviously Jimmy was into more than just baking cupcakes.
调查市内所有
So let's look at all the owners
68年道奇突击者车的车主
of '68 chargers in the metro area.
没问题
You got it.
莱恩在哪里
Hey, where's Ryan?
对了
Oh, right.
和罗森伯格医生约在20分钟后
The appointment at dr. Rosenberg's office is in 20 minutes.
要15分钟才能到
It's gonna take us at least 15 to get there,
我们应该出发了
So we should probably go, right?
这就是说你应该
Which means you should probably...
怎么了
Hey, what's the matter?
如果是我的问题呢
What if it's my fault?
如果结果是我有什么问题呢
What if it turns out that there's something wrong with me?
这不是任何人的错  凯文
It's nobody's fault, Kev.
我们只是需要知道到底是怎么回事
We just need to know what's going on.
需要帮忙吗
You want some help?
不错
Nice.
烘焙大师吉米·韦兰
So master baker Jimmy Whelan,
多年来售卖高热量的美味烘焙食物
longtime purveyor of caloric yet delicious baked goods,
当地街区少年垒球队的赞助人
sponsor of a local kids' softball team,
小生意圆桌会议的发起人
charter member of the small business roundtable--
但他怎么会有五万现金
But what was he doing with 50 grand in cash,
还要秘密前往斯坦顿岛
and why the secret trips to staten island?
听起来有秘密的不止你一个人  卡塞尔
Sounds like you're not the only one keeping secrets, Castle.
我准备忽略这句话
I'm going to ignore that.
这很奇怪
That's peculiar.
这有什么好奇怪的
What's so peculiar about wanting to ignore--
不是  我是说这些采购单
No, no, no, I mean these purchase orders.
这里写着吉米花了七万多
They show that Jimmy spent over $70,000
买厨房设备
on kitchen equipment.
比如说六米多宽的小型冷库
Like a 20-foot-wide walk-in freezer.
我好像没见过那东西
I don't remember seeing that.
因为根本就没有
That's because there wasn't one.
他厨房根本就放不下
It wouldn't even fit in his kitchen.
我查过那辆道奇车
Yo. So I ran '68 chargers.
城里只有几辆这款车  不过听好了
There's only a handful of them on the road, but get this.
其中有一辆在罗伯特·S·珊农名下
One of 'em is registered to a Robert S. Shannon,
也就是鲍比·S
A.K.A. Bobby S.
他是斯塔顿岛爱尔兰黑帮的首脑
He's a shot caller for the Irish mob over in Staten Island.
也是个心狠手辣的王八蛋
He's a ruthless son of a bitch, too--
贩毒  袭击他人
drug trafficking, assaults.
他是斯塔顿岛内一半凶杀案的嫌疑人
He's suspected of half a dozen murders over in Staten Island.
等一下  偷偷去斯塔顿岛
Wait a minute. Secret trips to Staten Island,
和那么多的钱
all that cash...
如果这个蛋糕店是黑帮洗钱的地方呢
What if the cupcake shop is actually a mob front?
蛋糕师吉米·韦兰
Jimmy Whelan the baker
其实是洗钱师吉米·韦兰
is actually Jimmy Whelan the money launderer.
鲍比·S可能跟他闹了别扭
Bobby S. could've had a falling out with him,
所以就把他弄死了
could've whacked him.
也许吧  但我们需要更多证据
Maybe, but we're gonna need more
不能因为他的车出现在犯罪现场
than just his car at the crime scene
就把他和谋杀连在一起
to connect him to that murder.
也许有人能帮我们
Well, I may have somebody who can help us out with that.
我找出了他的通话记录
I pulled Jimmy's phone records.
过去三天里  他接到了无数个电话
In the last three days, he received numerous calls
都是一个女人打来的  叫塞...
from a woman named, um... Sibhan...
塞
Siob--
塞博  赛博
Siob--Sib--
-雪芳  -雪芳
- Siobhan. - Siobhan?
爱尔兰人这点很"出名"
Yeah, the Irish are notorious
喜欢取读不出来的名字
for spelling names in wild and unpronounceable ways.
我不知道你是怎么念出
I don't even see how you get that from--
我也不知道
You're not alone.
雪芳·奥多
Anyway, Siobhan O'Doul,
她在斯塔顿岛开了间酒吧
she runs a bar over in Staten Island.
根据有组织犯罪科记录显示
And according to Organized Crime,
那是鲍比·S做生意的地方
it's a place where Bobby S. does a lot of his business.
酒吧是雪芳开的吧
Does Siobhan happen to own that bar?
是的
She does, yeah.
谢谢你能来  奥多女士
Thank you for coming in, Ms. O'Doul.
愿为纽约警察贡献微薄之力
Anything for New York's finest.
尤其是考虑到
Yeah, especially considering that
像妨碍司法这样的重罪指控
a felony charge like obstruction
会让你丢掉酒水贩卖许可证
would cost you your liquor license.
你想要什么
What do you want?
我需要从你这了解吉米·韦兰的情况
I need some answers about Jimmy Whelan.
没听过这个人
Never heard of him.
这可有意思了  因为过去三天里
That's funny considering you made seven phone calls
你给他打了七通电话
to him over the last three days.
蛋糕店的吉米
Oh, Jimmy the baker.
我想订一些纸杯蛋糕
Yeah, I-I'm thinking of ordering some cupcakes.
你没机会了  他被杀了
Yeah, well, you missed your chance. He was killed.
什么时候
When?
今天的早些时候
Earlier today.
你知道什么情况吗
Do you know anything about it?
不知道  我怎么会知道
No. Why would I?
我们认为一个经常去你酒吧的人
Well, we think that someone that
和这个案子有联系
frequents your bar was involved.
关于鲍比·S你知道什么
What can you tell me about Bobby S.?
我不会再多说一个字
I'm not saying another word.
把我的手机给我  我现在就要打电话
Give me my phone call. I want my phone call now.
伙计们
Hey, guys.
怎么了
Hey, what's up, man?
抱歉迟到了
Sorry I'm late.
和...那什么的事怎么样了
How did the, uh, thing go, with the, uh...
在那啥里那啥
You know, do the thing in the thing
再把那啥给医生
and give the thing to the doctor?
挺顺利的
Yeah. Uh, it went... fine.
你的小泳将们游得快吗
So are your swimmers swimming?
还不知道呢
Um, I don't know yet.
有案子啊
Hey, caught a case.
是的是的  有个案子
Yeah, yeah, as a matter of fact, we did.
让我给你科普一下
Let me bring you up to speed.
大伙好
Hi, guys.
你好啊  珍妮
Hey. Hey, what's up, Jenny?
凯文  你没带午餐
Kevin, you forgot your lunch.
谢了  宝贝
Thanks, baby.
要是没了我  你该怎么办
What would you do without me, huh?
费顿
Fenton?
雪芳
Siobhan?
费顿
Fenton.
你干什么呢
Hey! What the hell are you doing?
这是我老公
That's my husband.
你结婚了
You're married?
女士  不能扇警察的耳光
Oh, lady, you can't slap a cop.
你是警察
You're a cop?
骗子  你这个混蛋
You liar! You son of a bitch!
你怎么能这么做  放开我  放开我
How could you?! Get off of me! Let go!
听我解释
I can explain.
你们知道这是怎么回事吗
What do you know about this?
啥都不知道
Not a thing.
拜托
Come on.
咱们的莱恩有没有可能
Is it possible our Ryan
干出这么狗血的出轨事件呢
is involved in something scandalous and tawdry?
莱恩  不可能  他干不出来
Ryan? No way. He doesn't have it in him.
但是你没看到
Yeah, but did you see the way
雪芳给他狠狠地一吻吗
Siobhan gave him that flying lip lock?
他们  看  珍妮生气了
They--ooh. Look, Jenny's pissed.
这很正常
Yeah, well, it's not surprising
当你发现你的另一半也藏着秘密的时候
when you find out someone you're in a relationship with
你也会生气
is keeping a secret.
我
I...
淡定  他出来了
Be cool. Here he comes.
自然点  自然点
Act normal. Act normal.
很自然啊
I am. This is normal.
该死
Damn.
鲍比·S
Bobby S.
你们觉得是他
Are we thinking that this guy
除掉了吉米·韦兰吗
is the one that took out Jimmy Whelan?
等下  你认识鲍比·S
Wait. You know Bobby S.?
我们以前是朋友
Yeah, we were friends back in the day.
你和这种混蛋是朋友  怎么回事
You were friends with this lowlife? How's that?
我们以前在一个帮派里
We used to run in the same crew.
进凶案组之前
I was undercover for 14 months
我做过14个月的卧底
before I joined homicide.
你在斯塔顿岛做过卧底
You were undercover on Staten Island?
在爱尔兰黑帮
With the Irish mob?
是  关于鲍比·S我们还知道什么
Yeah. So what do we got on Bobby S.?
等等  等等
No. Hold on. Hold on.
继续前几句话
Just go back for a second, please.
你在那里卧底
You were undercover?
在那和雪芳...
That's where you and Siobhan used to--
这件事很复杂
It's complicated.
我就喜欢复杂
I love complicated.
雪芳和这件案子有什么关系
How is Siobhan connected to all this?
她认识死者
She knows the vic.
显然还认识鲍比·S
And she knows Bobby S., obviously.
但她不肯开口合作
But she's not talking.
或许她会愿意告诉我
Maybe she'll talk to me.
我猜你的真名不是费顿·奥康纳咯
So I guess it's not Fenton O'Connell.
是凯文  凯文·莱恩
It's Kevin. Kevin Ryan.
至少你是爱尔兰裔
Well, at least you're Irish.
关于这一点你没有撒谎
You didn't lie about that.
很多事我都撒谎了
I lied about a lot of things.
他们说你躲起来了
They said you went into hiding.
七年来杳无音信
Seven years without a word.
是啊  我知道
Yeah, I know.
你什么都不知道
You do not know.
相信我  我也不想走的
Believe me, I didn't want to go.
省省吧
Spare me.
你甚至都没种当面告诉我
You didn't even have the guts to tell me to my face.
只在梳妆台上留了一张纸条
Just a note on the dresser.
雪芳  我知道你很生气
Siobhan, I know you're angry.
但如果你陷入了麻烦
But if you're in trouble,
如果你知道鲍比·S跟凶案有关
if you know something about Bobby S. killing this guy,
告诉我
tell me.
让我帮你
Let me help you.
你去死吧
You can go straight to hell,
臭条子
Cop.
做卧底
Deep cover?
他居然没告诉过我
I can't believe he didn't tell me.
埃斯波  他甚至都没告诉珍妮
Espo, he didn't even tell Jenny.
但我是他的好兄弟  她只是妻子罢了
Yeah, but I'm his best friend. She's just the wife.
就是因为这种思想  你才一直打光棍
Thus proving why there is no Mrs. Esposito.
那是因为很难找到配得上我的女人
Hey, it's hard to find a woman for this much man.
谈得怎么样
So how'd it go?
没成功
It didn't.
那么
So, uh,
我们推测鲍比杀这家伙的动机是什么
what do we think Bobby's motive was for killing this guy?
我们不知道
We don't know.
但似乎他们为了什么事闹掰了
But it seems like the two of them had a falling out of some sort.
是啊  可以这么说
Yeah, you could put it that way.
请问你是哪位
And you are?
联调局特别探员萨姆·沃克
Special agent Sam Walker, FBI.
我是贝克特探长
I'm detective Beckett.
这是莱恩和埃斯波西托警探
This is detective Ryan and Esposito.
莱恩  凯文·莱恩
Ryan? Kevin Ryan?
-你听说过他  -当然了
- You've heard of him? - Yeah, of course.
这家伙带着窃听器潜入爱尔兰黑帮团伙
This man got inside the Irish mob with a wire
其他人都做不到
when no one else could.
你帮我们抓获了斯坦顿岛上一半的帮派成员
You helped put away half the crew in Staten Island.
只可惜野火烧不尽啊
Too bad the weeds grew back, huh?
他们向来如此
They always do.
联调局为什么对我们的凶案调查感兴趣
So what's the FBI's interest in our murder investigation?
你们的被害人吉米·韦兰
Your victim--Jimmy Whelan.
他是我的线人
He was my informant.
吉米本来安分地经营着小店
Jimmy was just running his shop,
勉强度日
trying to get by,
但后来经济严重滑坡
but then when the economy turned,
他借了高利贷
he borrowed some hard money,
那之后  鲍比·S就控制住他了
And after that, Bobby S. owned him.
那么吉米在向你报告鲍比的生意往来吗
So Jimmy was feeding you intel on Bobby's operations.
不仅如此
No, more than that.
他本来要帮助我们得到那本帮派"圣经"的
He was gonna help us get the crew's bible.
那本"圣经"
The bible?
我想你们说的一定不是那本圣书吧
I'm guessing we're not talking about the holy book.
不  是帮派成员的叫法
No, it was just something the crew called it.
是一份记载了多年交易和联络人的清单
It's a list of transactions and contacts going back years.
拿到那本圣经  就可以扳倒整个犯罪团伙
You get that bible, you'll take down the whole crew.
现在吉米死了  你又得从头开始了
So now that Jimmy's gone, you're back to square one.
差不多吧  不过我们还有雪芳
Pretty much, though we still have Siobhan.
不好意思   我没听明白
I'm sorry. I don't understand.
她也是我的线人
She's my informant, too.
什么  雪芳是不会告密的
What? Siobhan wouldn't snitch.
过去的雪芳或许不会
Maybe not the old Siobhan.
但事实上  你走后
But the truth is, once you left,
她很难过
she fell on hard times.
帮派成员都在她的酒吧喝酒
The crew drinks at her bar.
他们跟她聊天  信任她
They talk to her. They trust her.
鲍比·S甚至在她地下室设了一个办公室
Bobby S. even keeps an office in the basement.
她想挣脱出来时  我们提出了一项交易
So when she wanted out, we made an offer.
什么交易  证人保护计划吗
For what, witness protection?
是的  前提是她帮我们扳倒黑帮
Yeah, if she helps us bring down the crew.
她的出路就是帮我们拿到那本"圣经"
Helping us get the bible, that was gonna be her ticket.
直到鲍比发现吉米是个内奸
Well, until Bobby S. figured out that Jimmy was a rat
并且将他杀害了
and had him killed.
她打电话给吉米就是为这事吗  提醒他
So that's why she called Jimmy, to warn him?
是的
Yeah.
吉米自认为能说通鲍比
Jimmy thought he could talk his way out of it.
但显然  他失败了
Of course, he couldn't.
雪芳现在要怎么办
So what happens to Siobhan now?
她必须回去
She goes back in.
不行
She can't.
现在不行
Not now. I--
那太危险了
It's too dangerous.
她很清楚要面临的风险
She knows the risks.
沃克探员  如果我们能发现她和吉米的联系
Agent Walker, if we linked her to Jimmy,
那鲍比·S也能发现
Then Bobby S. can, too.
听着  雪芳可以选择抽身
Look, Siobhan is free to walk away.
去哪呢
And go where?
谁都别想轻易摆脱鲍比·S
You don't just walk away from Bobby S.
大家都知道那一点  他一定不会放过她的
Everybody knows that. He's gonna hunt her down.
你必须把她加入证人保护计划
You have to put her in witness protection.
拿到"圣经"后当然可以
Yeah, for the bible, sure.
但证人保护计划不是什么福利项目
But witness protection isn't some entitlement program.
雪芳必须自己争取
Siobhan has to earn it.
失陪了
Excuse me.
我需要立刻和她见面
I need to meet with her now.
联调局的人要置她的生死于不顾
The feds are hanging her out to dry.
鲍比一旦发现  肯定会杀了她的
And when Bobby finds out, he'll kill her for sure.
听着  雪芳
Look, Siobhan,
现在最重要的是不要慌张
The main thing is not to panic.
千万别做任何可能引起怀疑的事
You don't want to do anything that might arouse suspicion.
低调一段时间  你会没事的
Just keep your head down for a while. You'll be fine.
不
No.
你会死的
You'll be dead.
瞧瞧你  终于说实话了
Look at you, telling the truth.
那条子说得对  我现在死定了
The cop is right. I'm screwed six ways to sunday here.
鲍比·S把"圣经"放在哪
Where does Bobby S. keep the bible?
在他卧室的保险箱里
In his bedroom safe.
吉米原打算怎么拿到手
How was Jimmy gonna get it?
每周四  鲍比·S会找大伙去赌桌球
Every Thursday, Bobby S. has the guys over to bet on pool.
吉米本该在那时候下手
Jimmy was supposed to do it then.
密码是多少
What about the combination?
鲍比每周五都会改密码
Bobby changes it every Friday.
但我知道他的规律
But I know the system he uses.
吉米之所以能拿到圣经
And Jimmy could get the bible
是因为他是帮派成员
because he was one of the crew,
可以进入鲍比·S的房子
and he has access to Bobby S's house.
现在我们在内部没有人了
And now we got no one inside.
我去
I'll go in.
我去拿那本"圣经"
I'll get the bible.
真的吗
Really?
你  怎么做
You? How?
你知道我当年跟鲍比·S关系很铁
You know how close I was to Bobby S. Back then.
我作为费顿·奥康纳的身份并没有暴露
My Fenton O'connell cover is still good.
警探  那是七年前的事了
Detective, that was seven years ago.
帮派成员只知道
As far as the crew knows,
联调局找上门时我跑了
I bolted when the feds swooped in.
你们还起诉了费顿·奥唐纳  对吧
You guys even filed indictments against Fenton O'connell, right?
对
Yeah.
那本圣经我们找了多久了
How long has law enforcement been after that bible,
15年  20年
15, 20 years, huh?
这些家伙是毒瘤
These guys are drug-dealing parasites.
什么时候再有机会把他们一网打尽
When are you gonna get another shot to wipe 'em all out?
听着  你想要那本圣经
Look, you want the bible,
我们想缉拿凶手鲍比·S
we want Bobby S. for murder,
雪芳想继续活着
Siobhan wants to keep breathing.
人人获利
Everybody wins.
我可以做到
I can do this.
我去请示一下上级
Let me run this by my A.S.A.C.
你干什么
What are you doing?
你疯了吗
Are you out of your mind?
我当过费顿  我可以重扮一次
I was Fenton. I can be him again.
别为了我丢了性命
Don't get yourself killed on my account.
好吧  你恨我
Okay. Yeah, you hate me.
我知道  我活该
I get that, and I deserve it.
你想得到证人保护吗
But do you want to be put in witness relocation or not?
想不想
Yes or no?
警探
Detective...
你刚刚说的是认真的吗
Were you serious about that offer?
你已经很久没参与行动了  警探
You've been out of it a long time, detective.
组织发生了变化
There's a new hierarchy,
你必须尽快争取他们的信任
and you're going to have to win them over, fast.
你已经七年没扮费顿了
Seven years since you were Fenton--
太久了
That's a lifetime.
光扮演还不够
It's not enough to act like him.
你必须成为这个人
You must become him.
我就是费顿·奥康纳
I am Fenton O'connell.
如果你说服不了他们
If you're not convincing,
必死无疑
you're dead.
我就是费顿·奥康纳
I am Fenton O'connel.
我不喜欢这样  兄弟
I don't like this, bro.
你没戴窃听器  也没带定位器
You don't have a wire, no locator.
如果我戴这些  鲍比·S会发现的
If I did, Bobby S. would find 'em.
只能这样  伙计
This is the way it's gotta be, man.
那两个给你担保的沃克探员的线人
What's the name of Agent Walker's informants
叫什么名字
who will vouch for you?
梅森兄弟  马特和托尼
The Mason brothers, Matt and Tony.
最近一次在哪蹲的监狱
Where'd you do your last stretch?
埃尔迈拉  杀了一个人
Elmira for man one.
我还能告诉你我的手机号
I can even tell you my cell number.
我心里有数  好吗
I know what I'm doing, okay?
雪芳呢
What about Siobhan?
我们的计划没问题
Our plan is solid.
我能行
I got this.
那回头见  搭档
See you on the other side, partner.
怎么  就这么欢迎我吗
What, this is the welcome I get, huh?
你们这些爱尔兰混蛋都不想我吗
None of you Irish bastards missed me, huh?
费顿
Fenton?
费顿·奥康纳
Fenton O'connell?
雪芳
Hey, Siobhan.
也很高兴见到你  玛吉
Nice to see you, too, Maggie.
你还想要什么  列队欢迎吗
What'd you expect, a parade?
不想想你对雪芳干的混蛋事
After what you did to Siobhan?
你只能打一拳
Unh-unh. One shot's all you get.
放开那位女士
Hey, take your hands off the lady.
只要她别碍着我
Long as she keeps her hands off of me.
七年了  费顿
Seven years, Fenton?
你到底去哪里了
Where the hell have you been?
听着  你生气  我懂
Look, you're pissed. I get it.
可这事我们私下解决  好吗
But we'll work all this... out, maybe a little less publicly.
不过我得先找鲍比·S聊聊
But first I need to talk to Bobby S.
原来你回来是找鲍比的
Oh, that's why you came back, for Bobby?
让我谈好正事
Let me handle my business,
然后我把时间都给你
and then I'll have nothing but time for you.
你可真有魅力
Ah, you are such a charmer.
可如果你要找的是鲍比·S
But if it's Bobby S. you're after,
就得先和他的二把手谈
you're gonna have to go through his number two.
是吗  谁呢
Yeah? Who might that be?
我丈夫
My husband...
连姆
Liam.
跟你说  他不是我认识的莱恩了
I'm telling you, man. He's not the Ryan I know.
我说的不仅是他的发型和着装
And I'm not just talking about the haircut and the clothes.
他像是变了个人
It's like he's a different dude.
他就该是那样子
That's what he's supposed to be.
他进入角色了  他是费顿  那很好
He's in character. He's Fenton. That's good.
如果他还不够好呢
Yeah, but what if he's not good enough?
时隔七年  难免有所生疏
After seven years, he's gotta be rusty.
这些斯坦顿岛的家伙可不是吃素的
And these Staten Island boys are no joke.
两位  帮莱恩最好的方式
You guys, the best way to help Ryan
是给鲍比·S定罪
is by building a case against Bobby S.
可能比我们设想的棘手
That might be trickier than we thought.
鲍比·S的68款突击者有张电子付费通行卡
Bobby S's '68 Charger has an electronic E-Z Pass,
而且记录显示
and records show
突击者开车去扬克斯
the Charger drove to Yonkers
在上午十点通过乔治·华盛顿桥
via the George Washington Bridge around 10:00 A.M.
下午两点后才回程
It didn't make the return trip till after 2:00 P.M.
吉米在11点半到12点间遇害
Jimmy was killed between 11:30 and 12:00.
这帮鲍比洗清了嫌疑
That puts Bobby in the clear.
怎么可能
How is that possible?
托德在面包店门口看到的那辆车
The car that Todd saw outside of the bakery
一定是鲍比·S的
had to have been Bobby S's.
或许他想办法让电子付费通行卡失效了
Maybe he somehow disabled his E-Z Pass,
制造出他往返扬克斯的假象
making it appear as though all he did was go to and from Yonkers.
即便是这样  我们怎么证明呢
Okay, yeah, but how do we prove that?
我们查清他在扬克斯期间的去处
We figure out where he went when he was in Yonkers.
然后找证据
And then we find evidence
证明他在死亡时间区离开过那里
that he left during our time-of-death window.
他想制造不在场证明  我们就拆穿他
He's trying to build an alibi, and we're gonna tear it down.
把你手机给我
Give me your phone.
为什么
Why?
鲍比·S向来信不过电子设备
Bobby S. has an abiding distrust of electronic devices.
把你手机给我
Give me your phone.
这不是让人家生误会吗
Whoa. Whoa. What'll the missus think, huh?
鲍比
Hey, Bobby.
我认识你吗
Do I know you?
搞什么  是我  费顿
What the hell? It's me Fenton.
我记得多年前认识个费顿·奥唐纳
I recall knowing a Fenton O'connell years ago.
他待我情同手足
He was like a brother to me.
非常仗义的家伙
Real stand-up guy...
直到他跑路了
Till he cut and ran.
别这样  鲍比
Come on, Bobby.
我被出卖了  你知道的
I got ratted out. You know that.
我要留下来
Me hanging around
只会给大家都惹麻烦
woulda just brought more heat down on everyone.
所以你就人间蒸发了
So you made yourself scarce.
实际上  这七年里没人有你的音讯
In fact, no one's heard from you in... seven years.
你去哪里了
Where you been?
西部
Out west.
四处干了点小打小闹
Been making some moves here and there
直到过了诉讼时效
until the statute of limitations ran out.
老实说  鲍比
Tell you the truth, Bobby,
我要是手里没有好货
I didn't want to come home till I had something
都不好意思回来
to bring to the table.
朋友
Well, friend...
拿出来吧
Here's the table.
我听说联调局抓走了本·吉迪恩
I heard the feds took down Ben Gideon,
你可能需要一些货源
so you might be in need of some product.
我一直和梅森兄弟在芝加哥外奔波
I been working with the Mason brothers out of Chicago.
我听说过他们
I've heard of 'em.
这是稳定的货源  质量也不错
It's a stable source, quality stuff.
我可以帮你弄到一切你想要的
I can get you whatever you need.
我在扩展销路  鲍比
This is me stepping up, Bobby.
那又怎样
So what...
你就是歌里唱到的漂泊者
You're the wild rover from the song?
"满载着黄金而归"  是这个吧
"Returning with gold in great store," is that it?
要么你就是奸细
Or are you a rat?
你知道我不是这种人
You know me better than that.
这个嘛
Well...
该说的我都说了  我不会求你的  鲍比
I said my piece, but I'm not gonna beg, Bobby.
看你的了  好吗
It's up to you, okay?
是的  没错
Oh, yeah, it is.
那么
So...
我是应该欢迎浪子回家呢
Should I welcome home the prodigal son,
还是让连姆把子弹
or should I have Liam put a bullet
射进你的后脑
in the back of your head?
等着你下令呢  鲍比
Oh, just say the word, Bobby.
你要是觉得我是奸细
You think I'm some kind of rat,
一个不正直的人
that I'm a man without honor?
那就动手吧
Then you pull the trigger.
要是你怀疑我  鲍比
You doubt me, Bobby,
那你就亲自动手吧
you do it yourself.
费顿回来了
Fenton's back.
欢迎回家
Welcome home.
还在这呢
Still here.
要喝点什么
What can I get you?
一品脱黑啤酒
A pint of the black stuff.
请大家举杯
Glasses in the air.
卢克 15:32
Luke 15:32.
这算哪门子祝酒词啊
What the hell kind of a toast is that?
你在哪找到这傻帽的  鲍比
Where'd you find this heathen, Bobby?
他在主日学校读过书吗
Didn't he ever go to sunday school?
我在这欢喜地庆祝
"We should celebrate and rejoice
是因为
because..."
因为你在这的弟兄
"Because your brother here was dead
死而复生了
and has come to life."
欢迎回家
Welcome home.
-为了费顿  -费顿
- To Fenton. - Fenton.
一切安好
Slainte.
你怎么看他的
What do you think of him?
我怎么看无所谓  要看鲍比·S
Doesn't matter what I think. It's up to Bobby S.
是啊  可你相信他说的
Yeah, but do you buy his story
这七年他都在哪的故事吗
about where he's been for the last seven years?
我不知道  但我会去调查的
I don't know, but I'm gonna check it out.
要是他说谎了呢
And if he's lying about somethin'?
那我就杀了这个混蛋
Then I'll kill the bastard.
我想我知道鲍比·S去了扬克斯什么地方
So I think I figured out where Bobby S went in Yonkers.
去了跑马场
The Raceway.
他在那里的取款机取了500美元
He pulled out $500 in cash from the A.T.M. there.
去赌马了
Betting on the ponies.
停车场里有监控吗
Any security cameras in the parking lot?
埃斯波正在查  要是我们能证明
Espo's checking right now, but if we can prove
他恰好在案发时间离开
that he left just before our time-of-death window,
那就帮我们给他定罪了
then that should help us nail him for the murder.
不用了  谢谢  我很好
Oh, no. Thank you. I'm fine.
我们有莱恩的消息吗
So do we know how Ryan's doing?
没有  我讨厌有事情发生我却不知道
I don't know, and I hate not knowing things.
好吧  听着
Okay, look. Uh...
乔丹不是女的  行了吗
Jordan is not a woman, all right?
那他是谁啊  或者是什么啊
Then who is it? Or rather, what is it?
这重要吗
Why does it matter?
因为  卡塞尔  对你很重要
Because, Castle, it matters to you.
你就不能告诉我吗
Why won't you tell me?
蕾妮确定吉米·韦兰身上纤维的来源了
Lanie's identified the fibers on Jimmy Whelan.
是澳大利亚的羊毛制品
They are... wool from an Australian sheep.
也许鲍比有帮手
Ah, perhaps Bobby's had an accomplice--
一只冷血凶恶的绵羊
a cold-blooded, murderous sheep.
-就是这个  -真的假的
- That's it. - Seriously?
不是那个  看这个
No, not that. This. Look.
看他穿的外套
Look at the jacket he's wearing.
是皮革的
It's leather shearling...
上面有羊毛
with wool.
-这就和谋杀案联系起来了  -别急
- That ties him to the murder. - Not so fast.
跑道的贵宾停车区区
There were no cameras in the V.I.P. parking area
没有监控
of the racetrack.
但那天是鲍比·S的幸运日
But it turns out Bobby S had a lucky day.
40比1的概率他都赢了  赚了一万四
His 40-to-1 long shot won. Netted him 14 grand.
他穿着同一件外套
And wearing the same coat.
问题是
The problem is,
他填交税表格的时间
he's filling out his w-2g tax forms
与吉米被杀的时间一致
at the exact same time that Jimmy got whacked.
那鲍比就不可能是凶手了
Then Bobby can't be our killer.
他是被陷害的
So he was being set up.
有人借了鲍比·S的车  留下那些纤维
Someone borrowed Bobby S's car, planed those fibers,
这就是为了让他当替罪羊
All in an effort to make him look like the killer.
要是有人陷害鲍比
If someone's trying to set Bobby up,
莱恩就必须知道这一点
Ryan needs to know.
你知道这么见面很危险
You know... it's risky meeting like this.
最好是有重要的事
It better be important.
吉米不是鲍比杀的
Bobby didn't kill Jimmy.
真正的凶手偷了他的车然后陷害他
The real killer stole his car and set him up.
或者是鲍比命令别人做的
Or Bobby ordered the hit
把车借给了凶手
And loaned his car to the killer.
不是的  老兄
No, bro.
现场的证据是特意留下的
Forensic evidence was purposefully left behind.
这是陷害
It's a frame.
很可能就是他帮派里的人
Probably someone in his own crew.
好的  我会留心的
Okay. I'll keep my eyes open.
这对你有什么好处啊
What good is that gonna do you, hmm?
一旦那边发生了什么事  我不在你身边
What good is that gonna do you when something goes down,
这对你有什么好处啊
I'm not there to back you up?
你要做的就是放任不管
What you need to do is walk away.
等完事了我再离开
I'll walk away when I'm done.
你想什么呢
What's wrong with you?
你根本输不起 哥们  你有珍妮
You got a lot to lose, man. You got Jenny.
你还准备要个孩子
You're trying to start a family.
用不着你告诉我这有多危险
I don't need you to tell me what's at stake here.
听着
Look, man...
鲍比邀请我今晚和他去打台球
I got invite to Bobby's pool game tonight.
就等这个呢
This is it.
这是我拿到圣经的机会
This is my shot at getting that bible.
这不值得啊  伙计
It's not worth it, man.
到手了我就给你打电话
I'll call you when I get it.
鲍比怎么可能不是凶手
How could bobby is not be the killer?
我听他亲口说觉得吉米是奸细
I heard him say he thought jimmy was a rat.
肯定别人也听到了
Someone else must've heard that, too.
帮派里的人吗
Someone in the crew?
肯定是这样  对吧
It has to be, right?
这太糟了  你今晚不能去打台球了
This is bad. You can't go to the pool game tonight.
我必须去
I have to go.
我不会再有别的机会了
I won't get another chance.
这也是你唯一的机会
You won't get another chance.
鲍比保险箱的密码是多少
What's the combination to Bobby's safe?
3-0-4-2-1-7.
304217  你怎么知道的
3-0-4-2-1-7. How do you know that?
周五晚上鲍比会叫我打电话给他
Bobby has me ring up a total on the cash register
告诉他收银机里钱的总数
on friday nights.
他用总款数当做密码
He bases the combination on that total.
我们会顺利度过这一关的
We're gonna get through this.
不是吧  你还留着这个小家伙
Oh, come on. You still have this little guy?
等等  它叫什么名字来着
Wait. Um, what his name again?
你怎么能忘了胡子先生呢
How could you forget Mr. Whiskers?
你花了50刀才帮我赢回了他
You spent over 50 bucks trying to win him for me.
那个套圈游戏太坑爹了
That ring toss was a bitch.
但他物有所值
Well, it was worth every penny.
他陪伴我度过了不少难关
He's seen me through some pretty rough times.
我们的过去没有一点是真的吗
Was any of it real?
我对你的感情是真的
What I felt was.
我得走了
I gotta go.
今晚至关重要
Big night tonight.
在扬克斯跑马场的调查
So the canvass at Yonkers raceway
有了新发现
came up with something.
泊车员见过鲍比·S的黑色道奇车
A parking attendant saw Bobby S's black charger.
车子在案发半小时后返回
Now it returned 30 minutes after the murder.
他只是远远地看到了  但他说
He only saw it from a distance, but he says the driver
司机带着一顶棒球帽
Was wearing a baseball cap,
随后他步行去了地铁站
and he walked to the subway stop.
联系一下纽约交管局
Okay, let's touch base with the M.T.A.
联系过了
Already did.
我参照了那段时间里所有消费过的地铁卡
I cross-referenced all metrocards swiped at that time.
有一张是用信用卡购买的
One of them was bought with a credit card,
信用卡的主人是连姆·芬奇
and that credit card belonged to Liam Finch.
他是鲍比·S的二把手
That's Bobby S's number two.
这是一场阴谋
It's a coup.
连姆设计陷害鲍比来上位
Liam is framing Bobby to get him out of the way.
他想要掌权
He wants to take over.
而莱恩正好插手了这件事
And Ryan walked right in the middle of it.
不止如此  他不仅插手了
Worse. He didn't walk in the middle.
而且以鲍比·S朋友的身份搅局
He walked in as Bobby S's friend.
他自然成为了连姆的敌人
That makes him Liam's enemy.
我们得提醒他
Okay, we have to warn him.
如果我们打给他  他的身份就暴露了
If we call him, we could blow his cover.
如果不打电话  他会被杀的
If we don't, he could end up dead.
不是吧你
Get the hell outta here.
你的台球什么时候打得这么好了
Since when'd you become such a pool hustler?
请叫我"快杆艾迪"
Just call me Fast Eddie.
过来
Come here.
我看了你的报价  我能接受
I went over your numbers. I can live with 'em.
你多久能把货从芝加哥运过来
So how soon can you get some of that Chicago crank up here?
到这周末  我能弄到五磅
I can get you 5 pounds by this weekend.
下周的话
Come next week,
你想要多少  我就有多少
I can get you however much you want.
棒极了
Love it.
到你了  走狗屎运的混蛋
Take your shot, you lucky bastard.
基恩的电话  说有急事
It's Keane. Says it's urgent.
基恩  怎么了
Yeah, Keane.
连姆  你说得对
Liam, you were right.
有奸细
We got a rat in the house.
待会儿打给你
I'll call you back.
他说我们之中有奸细
He said we got a rat in the house.
好啦  我要去上厕所
All right, I gotta hit the head.
叫史迪威把车开到前门
Tell Stevie to bring my car around front.
体育干将  我正找你呢
Hey,sport. Been looking for you.
鲍比·S叫我们开车兜兜风
Bobby S needs us to take a ride.
好的  我去拿下手机
Okay. Let me get my phone.
你用不上手机
You're not gonna be needing it.
车子就在外面  你负责开车
Car's out back. You're driving.
好吧  我去去就来
All right. I'll be right back.
该走了  费顿
Time to go... Fenton.
莱恩还是不接电话
Ryan's still not answering.
如果鲍比·S不让人用手机
Well,if Bobby S doesn't allow cell phones in his presence,
那他可能还在和莱恩打台球
maybe he and Ryan are still just playing pool.
沃克特工说了什么
What did Agent Walker say?
联邦政府也不清楚莱恩在哪儿
The Feds don't know any more than we do about where Ryan is.
事情不太对劲
Something's not right.
凯文遇到危险了吗
Guys... Is Kevin in trouble?
没有
Uh, no.
我们只是在讨论些办案程序上的事
We're just talking some procedural stuff.
别骗我了  哈维  到底怎么了
Don't lie to me, Javi. What's going on?
我丈夫呢
Where's my husband?
珍妮  我们边喝咖啡边聊吧
Jenny, maybe we should go get a coffee.
那么你们不知道他在哪儿
So you don't know where he is?
是的  但是我们会找到他的
No. But we are going to find him.
我们认为他并没有遇到什么大危险
And,um,we don't believe that he's in any immediate danger.
他为什么要这样做
Why would he do a thing like this?
他可能是想证明些什么
Maybe he thinks he has something to prove
因为我的...怀孕问题
'Cause of all of our... pregnancy stuff.
我觉得其中有很多原因
You know,I think that there are probably a number of reasons,
但主要原因是  他想做对的事
But the main one is that he just wants to do the right thing.
那才是他  那是他当警察的原因
I mean,that's who he is, that's why he became a cop,
那正是你爱上他的原因
That's why you fell in love with him.
我只想他平安回来
I just want him to come home.
贝克特  我有话跟你说
Hey,Beckett. I need to talk to you.
我们要去码头吗
We going to the docks?
在码头只有两件事可做
Only two things to do at the docks--
杀人或是钓鱼
Kill someone or go fishing.
现在钓鱼有点晚了  不是吗
Kinda late to be fishing,ain't it?
是的  鱼儿都睡着了
Yep. All the fishies are asleep.
什么情况
What now,huh?
我一直对你有所怀疑
You know,I had my suspicions about you
自你踏进雪芳的酒吧的那刻起
from the moment you walked into Siobhan's bar.
可每个人都说费顿是纯爷们
But,no. Everybody said,"Fenton is stand-up. "
大家都相信你  包括鲍比·S
Everybody vouched for you,even Bobby S.
但你仍然怀疑我  是吧
But you still had your doubts,huh?
是的
That's right.
所以今天我让基恩跟踪你
So I had Keane follow you around today.
我知道我们之中有个奸细
You know,I knew that we had a rat amongst us.
但是我不明白的是
But what I didn't figure
他是怎么在我们眼皮子底下伪装的
was how that rat could hide in plain sight.
-雪芳  -对不起
- Siobhan? - I'm sorry.
我也是  兄弟
So am I,brother.
基恩跟着你去了雪芳的家
Keane followed you over to Siobhan's place.
是的  我和她的邻居聊天
Yeah,I spoke with one of her neighbors.
发现她两天前被警察抓住了
Turns out she was picked up by the cops two days ago.
基恩很好奇  所以闯进了她家
Being an inquisitive lad,Keane broke in to her place.
告诉他你的发现吧  基恩
Tell him what you found,Keane.
我翻了她的手机记录  费顿
I went through her cell phone,Fenton.
伙计  她曾和联邦调查局通过话
Man,she's been talking to the FBI.
这一切无疑是她捣的鬼
After all this time, nothing but a snitch.
犹大的内心
A judas...
天使的脸庞
With an angel's face.
费顿  你知道的  我很讲求公平
Now,Fenton,you know me. I'm nothing if not fair.
因此我给你一个公平的机会
So I'm gonna give you a fair chance
来证明你与此事无关
to prove you knew nothing about this.
打得她脑袋开花
Blow her brains out.
费顿  今晚不是她死
Fenton,we're leaving with one
就是你们一起死
or two bodies tonight.
全看你的说
It's up to you.
没关系的  我不怪你
It's okay. It's not your fault.
开枪吧
Just do it.
我做不到  鲍比
I just can't do it, Bobby.
我不能打死她
I can't shoot her.
但是我能够打死你
However I have no problem shooting you.
空弹匣  贱人
Empty. You son of a bitch.
以防万一  兄弟
Had to be sure, friend.
该死的  我对你太失望了  费顿
And damn. I'm so disappointed in you, Fenton.
你还会更失望的
Not as disappointed as you're about to be.
我的真名不是费顿
My name's not Fenton.
而是凯文·莱恩
It's Kevin Ryan,
我是警察
And I'm a cop.
什么  你是警察
What? A cop?
没错  而且我要逮捕你们三个
Yeah, and I'm placing the three of you under arrest.
想得美
Well, that'll be a hell of a trick,
考虑到连姆马上就要崩了你和你的女友
considering Liam's about to shoot you... and your girlfriend.
等等  连姆  先别动手
Wait a second. Liam, before you do that,
我先问你个问题  你的手机在哪儿
let me ask you a question. Where's your cell phone, huh?
什么
What?
还记得我们在大厅扭打的时候吗
Remember when we tussled back in the hall?
没错  我掏了你口袋
Yeah. I picked your pocket.
然后趁你不注意的时候
And then when you weren't looking,
我打给了我的搭档  让电话一直通着
I dialed my partner and left the line open.
不可能
No way.
我们要去哪儿  他听得清清楚楚
He heard exactly where we were going.
-连姆  -他在胡说  鲍比
- Liam. - He's full of crap, Bobby.
-他是吓唬我们  -是吗
- He's bluffing. - Oh, am I?
要不我们见见我的搭档吧
Why don't we meet my partner, huh?
喂  哈维尔  你在哪儿
Yo, Javi, where you at?!
我在这儿  哥们
Right here, bro.
别轻举妄动  他当过特种兵
No, no. He is former special forces.
你们不是他的对手
You do not want to draw on him.
还想见见其他伙伴吗
Want to meet the rest of my crew?
嘿  贝克特
Hey, Beckett!
莱恩  是你打的电话吗
You called, Ryan?
小子  别被她的美貌骗了
Don't let the looks fool you, boys.
你们也不是她的对手
You don't want to mess with her, either.
卡塞尔
Castle!
不是吧  我没带防弹衣
Seriously? I didn't... I didn't bring my vest.
放下武器  快
Drop your weapons. Now.
我有全纽约最好的律师
I got the best lawyer in New York.
我会被无罪释放的
I'm gonna walk.
联调局有了这个你跑不了
Not when I hand the Feds this.
一看这华丽丽的西装三件套就知道
Snazzy 3-piece suit could only mean one thing...
莱恩回来了
Ryan is back.
是啊  是啊
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
连姆审得怎样了
So where are we with Liam?
贝克特正在审呢  想让他承认
Beckett's got him in the box, trying to get him to confess
自己杀了吉米·韦兰
to Jimmy Whelan's murder.
沃克探员来电说  那本圣经真是好东西
And Agent Walker called. He said the bible you gave him is gold.
鲍比·S和他的同伙们都完蛋了
Bobby S and his whole crew are doing down.
哈维尔
And, uh, Javi...
那天在餐馆
The other day at the diner--
没事儿  当时那不是你本人
Don't sweat it. That wasn't you talkin', man.
那是费顿
That was Fenton.
谢谢理解
Yeah. Thanks.
你们一定不信  但连姆确实不是凶手
You guys aren't gonna believe this, But Liam is not our killer.
你说什么  可那确实是他的地铁卡啊
What are you talking about? It was his MetroCard.
他是用自己的信用卡付钱的
He paid for it with his own credit card,
他从鲍比车上下来后刷过卡
And then he swiped it after he dropped off Bobby's car.
我知道  但他有不在场证明
I know, but his alibi is solid.
他当时在斯塔顿岛
He was on Staten Island at that time.
如果他有不在场证明
Okay, well, if he has a solid alibi,
唯一的问题就是
the only question that remains is,
谁能拿到他的地铁卡
who had access to his MetroCard?
玛吉
Maggie...
我觉得你能干出很多事  但不会去杀人
You know, I pegged you for a lot of things, never a killer.
是啊  我也没想到你会是个缉毒大队长
Yeah, I pegged you for a lot of things, but never a narc.
其实我是凶杀案警探
Actually, see, I'm a homicide detective,
所以我知道你杀了烘焙师吉米
which is why I know that you killed Jimmy the Baker.
什么吉米
Jimmy the who?
老天  你还要和我们玩下去吗
Oh, god. Are we actually gonna play this game?
不早了  我都累了
It's late. I am tired.
警察搜了你家  找到了你的枪
Officers went through your house, And they found your gun.
和射杀吉米的枪口径一致
Same caliber that killed Jimmy.
迟早我们会查出两支枪弹道一致
It's only a matter of time before we get a ballistics match.
这么说  连姆不知道他老婆做了什么
So Liam had no idea what his wife was doing?
对  都是玛吉干的
No, it was all Maggie.
她知道连姆忠心耿耿
She knew that Liam was too loyal,
她觉得只有她把鲍比·S送进监狱
and she figured that if she could get Bobby S in prison,
她丈夫才能称王
her husband would ascend to the throne.
看来玛吉就像《麦克白》里的麦克白夫人
So really, lady Maggie was lady Macbeth,
不过她是爱尔兰人  不是苏格兰人
only she was Irish, not Scottish.
凯特  说起乔丹
Listen, Kate, about Jordan...
如果你不想说的话  就别说了
You know what? If, uh, if you don't want to talk about it--
我想谈  不过
No, I-I-I wanna, but...
如果你不喜欢你看到的会怎样
What happens if you don't like what you see?
如果你不让我看到会怎样
What happens if you don't let me look?
乔丹汽车公司  在1916到1931年间生产汽车
Jordan Motor Company. They made cars from 1916 to 1931.
这就是乔丹  所谓的大秘密  一家倒闭的公司
That's Jordan? That's the big secret, A defunct car company?
算是吧  这得追溯到我在寄宿学校上学的时候
Sort of. It goes back to my boarding school days.
那是第一个学期  我差点儿被退学
My first semester there, I was in danger of flunking out.
我期末考必须拿A
I needed an "A" on my term paper.
所以你就围绕那家公司写了篇文章
So you wrote the paper on that car company?
不  是别人写的
No. Someone else did,
然后我给了他250美元
and I paid him $250.
卡塞尔  这是你小时候的事
Um, Castle, that happened when you were a kid.
我没搞懂这怎么改变我对你的看法了
I don't understand why that would change how I see you.
因为它改变我对自己的看法了
Because it changed how I saw myself.
老师在班上读了我的文章
The teacher read the paper to the entire class
当成了优秀范文  大家为我鼓了掌
as an example of great writing, and they applauded.
那是我第一次被表扬
It was the first time I was celebrated ev--for anything,
但却是个谎言
And... it was a fraud.
我是个骗子
I... I was a fraud.
从那时起  我开始学写作
That's when I learned how to write.
我写啊写
I wrote and wrote,
努力让自己成为大家称赞的那个人
trying to be as great as everyone thought I was...
努力赢取称赞
trying to earn that applause.
我现在仍在努力
I'm still trying.
你说得对  卡塞尔  这确实改变了我的看法
You're right, Castle. It does change how I see you.
让我更喜欢你了一点点
It makes me like you just a little bit more.
别忘了胡子先生
Don't forget Mr. Whiskers.
你现在倒是记得他的名字了
Oh, so now you remember his name.
能让我俩聊会儿吗
Could you give us a second, please?
我正惦记着你能不能来呢
I was hoping you'd come.
这回我得道个别
I wanted to say good-bye this time.
道别让我觉得以后再见不到你了
"Good-bye" makes me feel like I'll never see you again.
确实啊
You won't.
明天  你就会到一个新的城市  有个新的名字
Tomorrow you'll be in a new city, have a new name.
你会重新开始
You'll get to start over again.
为什么你要这么做  为我冒生命危险
Why'd you do this, risk your life for me?
你知道的
You know why.
这个叫凯文·莱恩的家伙
This Kevin Ryan guy,
真希望再早点认识他
I wish I would've met him sooner.
对不起  珍妮
I'm sorry, Jenny.
我知道这对你不公平
I know it wasn't fair to you.
告诉我真相
Just tell me the truth.
你做卧底的生活结束了吗
Is this part of your life, this undercover part, over?
-是啊  结束了  -好
- Yeah, it is now. - Good.
因为我要知道你会在我身边
Because I need to know that you're gonna be here.
我要知道自己能依靠你
A-and I need to know that I can depend on you,
尤其是因为
Especially after the test results
产科医生给我们的检查结果
we got back from the fertility doctor.
-不  坏消息吗  -是啊
- Oh, no. Bad news? - Yeah.
我们做那检查真是瞎折腾一场
We took all those damn tests for nothing.
我已经怀孕了
I'm already pregnant.
你怀孕了
You're pregnant?
You're pregnant.
我们开香槟吧
Let's, uh, let's pop some champagne.
不行  我们不能喝香槟
No. We can't pop any champagne
你知道的  因为
You know why...because...
-你怀孕了  -我怀孕了
- You're pregnant. - I'm pregnant.